(Penny:)...he can't go here
because of my pointy-head guy.
(Leonard:)Like I said, complicated game.
- So did I win or not?
- Did you have fun?
(Leonard:)Because if you had fun,
then you are a winner.
(Leonard:)That's what chess is all about.
- Hello.
- Hey.
(Penny:)Oh, hey. Sorry, Sheldon, I'll move.
(Sheldon:)Why? My spot, your spot.
What difference does it make?
- Okay, what just happened?
- l don't know.
(Leonard:)Between you playing chess
like Bobby Fischer...
(Leonard:)...and Sheldon being okay
with you in his spot...
(Leonard:)...I'm guessing
someone went back in time...
(Leonard:)...stepped on a bug,
and changed the course of human events.
(Penny:)- Sweetie, are you all right?
- No, I'm not all right.
(Sheldon:)It's been six days
since I was supposed to get a haircut...
(Sheldon:)...and nothing horrible has happened.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm sorry, I don't understand.
- Leonard, explain it to her.
- Oh, uh, he's crazy.